<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rebuild schools and hospitals in Kharkiv</title>
    <link>http://something-fresh.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rebuild schools and hospitals in Kharkiv</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://something-fresh.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cookies</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/cookies/</guid>
      <description>LAST UPDATED: March 18, 2022
Cookies are small text files that are stored on your device. They enable to store some information on your device that is accessible only by a web server of a specific domain. Cookies neither can run the code on your device nor are able to transmit viruses to your device.
Our website use only limited types of cookies, namely analytical cookies. We use these cookies to improve your experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/donate/</guid>
      <description>Paypal Donate via PayPal     Transfer via Revolut Donate via Revolut     SEPA bank transfer Direct bank transfer from EU/EFTA is possible. Please contact us for bank details.    We strongly encourage getting familiar with our mission before donating. If you have any questions about donation, please do not hesitate to write to us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal information</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/legal/</guid>
      <description>LAST UPDATED: March 30, 2022
Organization Our fund is currently in the process of registering as a German nonprofit organization in a form of gUG (gemeinnützige Unternehmergesellschaft).
Image on the front page A Hospital &amp;amp; School © 2020 by Cindy Wang is licensed under CC BY-NC 4.0 🙏
The image was modified: Ukrainian flags 🇺🇦 were added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our contributors</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/contributors/</guid>
      <description>LAST UPDATED: March 15, 2022
List of incredible organizations:
   List of incredible individuals:
 Cindy Wang Ilia Azizi  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our mission</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/mission/</guid>
      <description>LAST UPDATED: March 15, 2022
Introduction On February 24, 2022, Russia has launched a full-scale war against Ukraine. Despite false claims by the Russian government that only military objects will be targeted, the Russian army intentionally shelled and killed civilians. The Office of the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights has recorded 1&#39;834 civilian casualties in the country (691 killed and 1&#39;143 injured)1. As of March 14, Mariupol alone lost 2&#39;357 human lives2 according to Mariupol City Council.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/privacy/</guid>
      <description>LAST UPDATED: March 18, 2022
Your data privacy is a priority for us. We value your rights of data protection and do our best to secure your data in any meaningful way.
We collect only the necessary information and minimize the collection of your personal information. For example, we do not collect such identifiable information as names, physical addresses, birthdays, telephone numbers, credit card details, etc. On the other hand, we do collect your email address to provide acknowledgments, since it is crucial for our fund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign up for volunteering</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>If you are willing to help, we will be very happy to arrange it. Currently, we are looking for any collaborations with individuals and organizations who specialize in architecture, construction, education, and healthcare.
Further, we are planning to organize summer camps for volunteers during the summer time.
Please contact us via email to know more details: rebuild@schoolsandhospitals.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual evidences of destroyed schools and hospitals</title>
      <link>http://something-fresh.org/evidences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://something-fresh.org/evidences/</guid>
      <description>.scroll-container{ overflow: auto; white-space: nowrap; padding: 5px 70px 5px 20px; background: transparent; height: 320px; border-radius:15px; } .gridscroll{ display:inline-block; } .gridscroll img { height: 300px; width: auto; margin-right:22px; }  📣 🇺🇸 On this page, you can find collected visual evidences of destroyed schools and hospitals.
If you have any visual evidences of schools or hospitals damages in Kharkiv, please submit them using this link.
‼️ Since these images might be used by the Russian army to adjust their targets, we will post images with the delay.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
